module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'the world record for most babies born by a human woman is', 
      a: '18', 
      b: '23',
      c: '26',
      d: '69',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'the longest throw of a disc golf frisbee stands at a whopping', 
      a: '570 ft', 
      b: '722 ft',
      c: '836 ft',
      d: '1,012 ft',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'when asked what the inspiration was for the band ween\'s seminal record "the pod" was, they responded with', 
      a: 'their friend\'s super hot mom', 
      b: 'huffing scotchguard',
      c: 'david hasselhoff',
      d: 'poutine',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'in 1999, civil engineer david phillips earned over one million airline miles by', 
      a: 'taking 61 round trip flights from los angeles to sydney', 
      b: 'winning a televised game show sponsored by an airline',
      c: 'settling a lawsuit with an airline company',
      d: 'buying 12000 cups of pudding',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'the los angeles dodgers\' team name refers to', 
      a: 'people jumping out of the way of streetcars', 
      b: 'avoiding the military draft',
      c: 'the auto company that originally owned the team',
      d: 'corndodgers, the cake made of indian corn and wrapped in husks',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'the south park episode "more crap" centers around who can poop the largest amount. the unit of measurement in this competition is called', 
      a: 'philbins', 
      b: 'stallones',
      c: 'courics',
      d: 'winfreys',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'did jeffrey epstein kill himself?', 
      a: 'yes', 
      b: 'no',
      c: 'maybe',
      d: 'he\'s still alive',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'rock star george harrison\'s song "layla" is about', 
      a: 'queen elizabeth', 
      b: 'his cousin',
      c: 'george harrison\'s wife',
      d: 'his high school crush',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'while most consider it to be embellished, nba great wilt chamberlain once boasted to have slept with how many women?', 
      a: '20,000', 
      b: '2,000',
      c: '200',
      d: '20',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'which of the following places does the lotion go?', 
      a: 'on its skin', 
      b: 'under the basket',
      c: 'down the well',
      d: 'in the hose',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};